(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
Nerissa Ravencroft
Koseki Bijou
Shiori Novella
Mori Calliope
Oozora Subaru
Ookami Mio
Aki Rosenthal
Shirakami Fubuki
AZKi
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026
Ruffians!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau yeah
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yuppy sisters!
Lifetime Showtime
FUWA!
MOCO!
BAU!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA!
MOCO!
I love being tricky doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau
一生涯 sing with you
Sing with you for a lifetime
Stars wink moon spotlight furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau yeah
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yuppy sisters!
Woooo...
BAU!
Way back then, all locked up
we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept smiles away
...dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
But my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why いつだって It's that day! Today!
And that's why it's always that day! Today!
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! BAU! BAU!
一生涯 walk with you!
I'll walk with you for a lifetime!
Good times and bad times it doesn't matter!
いつだって It's that day! Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday!
It's always that day! Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday!
BAU! BAU! ジャン！ふたりは Happy lucky puppy sisters!
BAU! BAU! Ta-da! We are the happy lucky puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU! Everybody BAU!
Hallo hallo BAU BAU! Everybody BAU!
ダメダメノンノン Don't touch the ears!
No, no, no, no! Don't touch the ears!
モフモフノンノン Don't touch the tail!
Fluff, fluff, no, no! Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！BAU!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
フワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！BAU!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! BAU!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! BAU!
And together we're FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going fur-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Fufu! It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
Fufu! It's showtime! I want to be with you
Fufu! It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
Fuwa fuwa moco moco hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it won't forget our pledge to you
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! BAU BAU!
一生涯 sing with you!
I'll sing with you for a lifetime!
Stars wink, moon spotlight, fur-ever glow
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! BAU BAU!
And together we're fluffy fuzzy puppy sisters!
Let's hear you! BAU BAU!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO! YEAH!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO! BAU BAU!
Bau-bau! Ruffians! Abba!
Welcome to our FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate our birthday with us! Bau-bau!
始まりました！
It's finally starting!
今日は生誕ライブに来てくれてありがとう！Thank you!
Thank you for coming to our birthday live concert today! Thank you!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's variety show, tonight again, today we have a big concert!
And can you believe it? It's already been three years! Right, our third birthday in Hololive English!
Ah, Mococo-chan, we can't forget that really important thing, right?
Huh? Ah, the talk show? Ah, yeah, okay!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
We're Hololive English Advent's twin demon guard dog sisters! Together we're FUWAMOCO! BAU BAU!
And we have an amazing birthday festival stage here! Amazing stage! Amazing!
Wow-pfu! It's so big! And such a big booth too!
Ah, Fuwawa, look! Can we? Okay, here we go! 3, 2, 1...
BAU BAU!
It's so big and wide too! Thank you for being so big here today! But...
Ah, singing and dancing today is not just going to be us, right? No, we're also here with some very special guests too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来てるから楽しみにしててくださいね！
That's right, we have some very wonderful guests with us today, so please look forward to it!
そして、もう一人謎のゲストさんも…誰かな？Abba! Oi! Bau!
And also, one more mysterious guest... I wonder who it is? Abba! Oi! Bau!
But a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right? Right, something very important! Ah, I think you know what? WHAT?
Hashtag! Yeah! The birthday hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag: #FWMCbday26! That it is!
ぜひハッシュタグで感想呟いてください。写真もね。あとでポチしに行くから。Bau-bau! Check them all!
Please be sure to tweet your thoughts with the hashtag. Photos too! We'll go and 'like' them later! Bau-bau! Check them all!
See you at the concert after the show!
Bau bau!
And...
Also, we're going to be having a special membership-only concert right after this, so don't miss it, okay?
Yeah! Uh!
最後にはメン限のアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
Lastly, there will be a members-only encore live, so please come watch!
Bau bau! Woah! Uh!
You know, it is a concert after all, right? So we should get singing a little bit more, yeah?
Yeah! Yeah! (Hehe)
Bau! Oh!
But for this next song, I think we need a special guest with us, right?
Yeah! Uh, okay!
Let's call her on together!
せーの！
Ready, set!
Calliope-senpai!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Abau!
皆さーん！バウバウ！
Everyone! Bau bau!
Today only, I am also a dog.
Bau bau bau bau! Shinigami dog!
Yeah!
Thank you for inviting me! I'm happy to be here! What's up, Ruffians?!
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh?
Wow, look at this logo. What could it say? Check it out!
Yo, respect, respect, respect, with respect, with respect!
But you know, it might be cute if we matched, right?
Maybe we'll just go run and we'll get changed into what she's wearing for a second?
Okay, entertain them!
You can do it!
They won't bite! It'll be okay!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment. 行くぞ！
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment. Let's go!
できないかも！できない！I can't! I'm sorry, I can't! I can't do it!
I might not be able to! I can't! I can't! I'm sorry, I can't! I can't do it!
I did my best. We're back! We're back!
But I can't... I can't do the splits.
But now, we're matching!
Twinning!
Triplet-ing!
That's a nice ring to it.
Um, this next song is one that FUWAMOCO we wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Something nostalgic, and I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap in there as well!
Oh yeah! Yeah! But it's also very cute, right?
次に歌う曲は、カリ先パイと一緒にずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！
The next song is a favorite song that I've wanted to sing with Calli-senpai for a long time!
そうね！
Right!
It's both cute, it's cool.
But I think you know, it shares an important part that, you know, you should be proud of what you like, right?
Important meaning of being proud...
...being strong about what you like, yeah! Your likes!
No matter what they be... Games! Anime! Idol!
Figures! Or maybe even... VTubers!
Oh! Nice! You were in sync there. Abau!
After all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right?
Um, we're going to sing this song for you guys!
Okay, let's do the title call together, okay?
聴いてください！
Please listen!
Like! Like! Like!
Comic, I Like it!
Music, I Like it!
Game, I Like it!
Animation, I Like it!
Figure, I Like it!
Movie, I Like it!
Wonder, I Like it!
Hobby, I Like it!
go go go go...
do you like it? I like it!
実生活 送るのも楽じゃないわ
Living real life isn't easy either
好きなもの 好きって言えたらそれスーパーノヴァ
If I can say I like what I like, that's a Supernova
快感中枢 即マックスのバース
Pleasure center, immediate max verse
待ちに待った かけがえのない時間と歌うバンバンバン
Singing 'bang bang bang' with the long-awaited, irreplaceable time
プラス マジック 踊り出せば 夢中 駆け抜けろ 一生ショー
Plus magic, if you start dancing, run through absorbed in a lifetime show
悩みさえ 煌めくのさ 今すぐ Let's make some noise
Even worries will sparkle, right now Let's make some noise
君が部屋にいたって メン限すればコンサート
Even if you're in your room, if you do a members-only stream, it's a concert
いつだって Lonely only Lonely only just don't know but say it's you!
Every day is Lonely only Lonely only just don't know but say it's you!
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If I fall in love
きっと 全てが カラフルで
Surely everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even the stardust
光る宝物なのさ
It's a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
やっと 今日から よろしくね
Finally, from today, nice to meet you
ほら キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling like a dream
早く 抱きしめたい
I want to hug you soon
あれもこれも欲しくて
I want this and that
神様に祈る
I pray to God
…待ってる
...waiting
いいね、好きでしょうがない
Nice, I just can't help liking it
次は、何にしようかな
I wonder what I should do next
I'll be back, world at night, took 'em all away, yo
飛ばさい、言葉払い、Cry Cry、okay?
Blowing away the bad words, Cry Cry, okay?
360度パノラマ、全方向大好きのシーン
360-degree panorama, a scene of loving every direction
何が一つでもいいから、のめり込める自分のアイテム
Just one thing is fine, my own item I can immerse myself in
Like a superstar fire man、無敵キャンディ、他は大体来世
Like a superstar fire man, Invincibility Candy, the rest in the next life
望んでる彼もきっと現世が愛おしくなるはずなのさ
The guy he's wishing for will surely find this life lovable too
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない、人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
It's not something you try to become, let's just enjoy walking through life
自分に素直であれ、Spotlight、僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, Spotlight, shine on us
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ、Get down!
Today again, I'm just shouting out love, Get down!
This is a song for you!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
I'm sure everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
夢の物語さ
Is a story from a dream
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
「ずっと、離さないでいてね」
“Never let me go, okay?”
ほら、キラキラ虹みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow
世界はまわりだす
The world begins to turn
行くぞ！
Let's go!
ガッチャコ、ガッチャコ！
Gatchako, gatchako!
わちゃわちゃパワー！
Wacha wacha power!
やーやーやー！
Yah yah yah!
スキ、スキ、スキ、勝負だ、手に入れたい
Like, like, like, it's a showdown, I want to make it mine
この感情、歯止めさえ、ガチンコ真剣勝負
This feeling, even the brakes, a real serious fight
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ？
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう、恋も猛烈実験
Yes, love is also a intense experiment
でもそれが僕の等身大
But that's my true self
ガチ、素晴らしい世界を確認
Seriously, confirming a wonderful world
いわゆる一、つの萌え要素
A so-called single 'moe' element
素直になれたなら、Happy Days
If I could be honest, Happy Days
I Like It! I Like It! スキになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you fall in love
きっと全てがカラフルで
I'm sure everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust
光る宝物さ
Is a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
やっと今日からよろしくね
Finally, from today, nice to meet you
ほら、キラキラ夢みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a dream
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hold you soon
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
I'm sure everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
夢の物語さ
Is a story from a dream
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
ずっと離さないでいてね
Never let me go
ほら、キラキラ虹みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow
世界はまわりだす
The world begins to turn
ハイ散歩！
Haisanpou!
Yeah! Yeah!
ハイ散歩！
Haisanpou!
エヘッ！
Eheh!
I like FUWAMOCO!
フワモコ・ハイ散歩！
FUWAMOCO Haisanpou!
バイバイバウバウ！バイバイ！
Bye bye bau bau! Bye bye!
ウフフッ！
Ufufu!
Please listen to our next song. Jo t'aime ★ jo t'aime.
Jo t'aime ★ jo t'aime
Lyrics: Tommy february6
Music: MALIBU CONVERTIBLE
街角にならぶ
Lining up on the street corner
映画のポスター
Are movie posters
もうこの街にも
Already, of this town too
飽きたわ
I'm bored
砂漠の向こうに
Beyond the desert
ため息をお返し
I return a sigh
キャンセルしないで
Don't cancel it
Mon amour pour toi
My love for you
ハートのポケットに
In the pocket of my heart
隠した写真
Is a hidden photo
誰も知らない
Nobody knows
本気の恋 神様は気づいてる
This serious love, God has noticed
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
I love you ★ I love you
叶わない夢なんて
A dream that won't come true
見たくないわ
Is something I don't want to see
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up
“愛してるわ”
“I love you”
クレープに描く
I draw on a crepe
愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the rain that won't stop
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんて
A boring romance is something...
したくないわ
...I don't want to have.
あっと言う間に
Before I knew it,
溺れてく
I'm drowning in it.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before the café au lait...
しまうその前に
...gets cold.
もう一度
Give me one more...
KISSして
...kiss.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Locking the story away.
je vous en prie
あなたのことばかりを
All I do is...
夢見ている
...dream of you.
mon amour
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて
Dreams that won't come true...
見たくないわ
...I don't want to see them.
でもロマンス
But romance...
目覚めてゆく
...is waking up.
愛してるわ
I love you.
クレープに描く
Drawing on a crepe,
愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love.
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of rain that won't stop.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
mon amour pour toi
退屈な恋なんて
A boring romance is something...
したくないわ
...I don't want to have.
あっと言う間に
Before I knew it,
溺れてく
I'm drowning in it.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before the café au lait...
しまうその前に
...gets cold.
もう一度
Let me hear you...
聞かせて
...say it once more.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
La la la...
Bau! Wow! Look at this sunset!
Oh, it's setting already, huh?
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was "je t'aime ★ je t'aime"!
Oh, what did you think, Ruffians?
What did you think, Ruffians?
It was a little bit more nostalgic.
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
Who knows? Some City Pop vibes too!
Yeah! Oh, the choreography is cute too, right? Oh, wow!
We hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy, Ruffians.
Yeah! Wow!
You know, with the sun setting now,
it's starting to feel a bit romantic almost, right?
Wow! I guess it's the perfect time to call up my next guest!
Yeah! Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! Akirose-senpai!
Yeah! Welcome!
Happy birthday! FUWAMOCO!
Congratulations on your 3D Live! Congratulations!
おめでとう！ お邪魔します！
Congratulations! Thanks for having us!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourselves!
はい！ こっこっこっAZKi、AZKiです！
Okay! Go-go-go-AZKi! It's AZKi!
Yeah!
ホロライブ1期生のアキ・ローゼンタール、
Hololive 1st Gen's Aki Rosenthal,
アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！ ヤッホー！
aka Akirose, Aki Rosenthal, daze! Yahoo!
Wow! Bau! Bau!
AZKi-senpai, Akirose-senpai, thank you so much!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
すごかったよ、ステージも！
The stage was awesome too!
Thank you! すごいね！
Thank you! It's amazing!
ね、AZKi先輩とアキロゼ先輩の歌声が、すごく大好きなので...
Yeah, we love AZKi-senpai and Akirose-senpai's singing voices so much, so...
嬉しい！ ありがとう！
We're so happy! Thank you!
次の一曲が、すごく...
The next song is very...
えっと、まあ...
Well, you see...
アキロゼ先輩とAZKi先輩は、とっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので、
Aki-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such charming older sisters,
あら！
Oh my!
本当ですか？
Really?
ぜひ、ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました！
so I really wanted to do this song with you both!
あらあら、あらあら。
Oh my, oh my.
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし。
The sun is starting to set, too.
確かに。ちょっと夕方、ロマンチックになりますね。
True. It's getting a bit romantic this evening.
おぉ、おぉ！実はちょっぴり、セクシーかも？
Oh, oh! Actually, it might be a little sexy?
セクシーかも？セクシーな曲？
Sexy? A sexy song?
おっ、したいことある？
Oh, is there something you want to do?
何かしたいこと、したいことありますか？何、何？
Is there something you want to do? What is it?
アキロゼ先輩！えっと、この曲を歌う前に、
Aki-senpai! Well, before we sing this song,
少し、あの、セクシーなウォームアップ...
I was thinking of a little sexy warm-up...
教えていただけますか？いただけますか？
could you teach us one?
セクシーウォームアップ？OK！いいですよ！
A sexy warm-up? OK! Sure!
じゃあ、まずセクシーな体を作るために、
Well, first, to get our bodies into a sexy mode,
自分のボディを撫でて！
caress your own body!
撫でて？撫でて！頭撫で撫で...
Caress? Caress! Starting from the head...
足から、足から！おー！足から！
From the legs, from the legs! Oh! From the legs up!
撫でる！撫でてみて！撫でて！
Caress! Try it out! Caress!
恥ずかしい...撫でて！アキロゼ先輩見て！
It's embarrassing... Caress! Look at Aki-senpai!
やってるやってる！あ、モコちゃん可愛い！いいよ！
She's doing it! Ah, Moco-chan is so cute! Nice!
いいよいいよー！最高！
Nice, nice! Perfect!
セクシー、撫でるのがセクシー。足から、足から。おーいえー！
Sexy, caressing is sexy. From the legs. Oh yeah!
モコちゃんもう一回、もう一回！
Moco-chan, one more time, one more time!
えー？うわぁー！ちょっと違うかな？
Eh? Waaaah! Is that not quite it?
あ、AZKiちゃんも何かセクシーだけど可愛い。ちょっと入りましたね。
Ah, AZKi-chan is also somehow sexy but cute. She's got it.
えー？やっぱこうやって...お、こう？
Eh? I guess like this... Oh, like this?
おー！セクシー！いいよいいよー！おー！
Oh! Sexy! Nice, nice! Oh!
あとしっぽ、あとしっぽ、しっぽ！しっぽフリフリも！
And the tails, the tails, the tails! Shake your tails too!
しっぽフリフリも！モコちゃんしっぽフリフリ！
Shake your tails too! Moco-chan, shake your tail!
ウォームアップ！プリプリプリプリ...
Warm-up! Wiggle wiggle wiggle...
OK、OK！いいんじゃない？いいよいいよー！準備できたー！
OK, OK! Isn't that good? Nice! We're ready!
じゃあ、いい感じになりましたね！
Well, that set the mood nicely!
はい！次の曲行きましょうか！はーい！
Yes! Shall we move on to the next song? Yes!
じゃあ、聴いてください。『DISCOTHEQUE』！
Then, please listen. 'DISCOTHEQUE'!
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
DISCO BABY, DISCO BABY
DISCO MOTION, DISCO MOTION
DISCOTHEQUE
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN' Let's dance
はじける BEAUTY LADY
The sparkling BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩りたいの
I want to color it softly
グラマラスな唇
Glamorous lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Pink glossy nails
ガラスの向こう側に
On the other side of the glass
映る素顔 シュールなデイズ
My face reflected in the surreal days
君だけにそっと 見せていたい
I want to show only you quietly
心の中 瞳の奥
Inside the heart, deep in the eyes
そばにいてほしいよ 黄金のミラーボール照らされて
I want you by my side, illuminated by the gold mirror ball
MY DARLIN' VIVIDな恋しましょう
MY DARLIN' Let's have a vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE ほら
Softly coloring MY LOVE, look
世界は変わる
The world changes
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
ロマンティックな呪文に
In the romantic spell
汗ばむデジャヴ 見続けたくて
Sweaty deja vu, I want to keep watching
カラフルなシティ・ストーリー
A colorful city story
心深く刻み込む
Etched deep in the heart
小さな闇が訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the love spell
きっと 果てない空 星屑のシャワーが降り注ぐ
Surely, a shower of stardust from the endless sky will pour down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So let's aim for HAPPY STATION
50/50 あわせて
50/50 combined
100%以上の愛
More than 100% love
揺るぎない心がここにあると
Knowing that an unwavering heart is here
私思ってる
I believe
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
CHURU-CHURU CHURU-PAYAPA
ブラブラしぶとく 恋焦がれて ブラブラ
Hang around tenaciously, pining for love, hang around
キミにはありのまま 好きでいて欲しいと
I want you to love me just as I am
願いを...
Making a wish...
素敵な...
Something wonderful...
CHU-CHU-DANCING
JUST MOVE IT MOVE IT
ON ME...
My Darling もっと一緒に踊りましょ
My Darling, let's dance together more
Secret Night 素敵な
Secret Night, wonderful
エピソードのような デコレーション
A decoration like an episode
二人のハート 惹かれ合わせて
Attracting our two hearts together
My Darling 眩いほど恋しましょ
My Darling, let's fall in love so much it's dazzling
弾ける Sexy Beauty
Bursting Sexy Beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢
A sweet dream, born anew
そっと色取る My Love ほら
Gently coloring My Love, look
世界は変わる
The world changes
CHURU-CHURU CHURU-PAYAPA
Kiss me 愛してる
Kiss me I love you
燃え尽きるわ この恋多分
It'll probably burn itself out, this love
どんな結末が来ようと 覚悟してる
Whatever the outcome may be, I'm prepared
余裕なんて ほとんどない
I have almost no composure at all
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on
あなたの目 優しく抱き寄せる腕
Your eyes, the arms that gently embrace me
全てが すべてが 初めての
Everything, everything is the first
My Love... Startは...
My Love... The start is...
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let me go
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just naturally
この不安も 拭い取ってね ねえ
Wipe away this anxiety too, okay?
Touch me その指先
Touch me, with those fingertips
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me, with that look in your eyes
この私を包み込んで Please
Wrap around me, please
愛してる
I love you
蘇るわ きのうのこと
It all comes back to me, what happened yesterday
あんなに心が揺れたの 初めてだもん
It's because it was the first time my heart wavered so much
淋しすぎて 時に恐い
It's too lonely, sometimes it's scary
二人でいれないこの時が
The times when we can't be together
雨の朝 あたたかな部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room
大人のふりから
From pretending to be an adult
本当の大人になれそう
It feels like I might actually become one
Kiss me 危険なほど
Kiss me, to a dangerous degree
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, with a sweet kiss
この願いを全部叶えて ねえ
Grant all of these wishes of mine, okay?
Knock me その唇で
Knock me, with those lips
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window
この私を安心させて Please
Give me peace of mind, please
愛してる
I love you
Kiss me... いけないほど
Kiss me... so much it's wrong
Kiss me... 甘いくちづけ
Kiss me... a sweet kiss
こんな願いを全部叶えてね
Please grant all these wishes
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Love me... そのまぶしい手
Love me... those dazzling hands
Love me... 窓をたたいて
Love me... knocking on the window
この私を安心させて Please
Please put me at ease
Please Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you
Ruffians! Are you ready?
Let's hear you!
Please enjoy!
Triangle Dreamer!
Day by Day 日に日に募るの 乙女心
Day by Day, a maiden's heart grows day by day
同じクラス 斜め前の おとなしい人
In the same class, the quiet person sitting diagonally in front
格好良くはない だけど優しい いつも頼れる彼
He's not cool, but he's kind, the guy I can always count on
放課後 内緒の帰り道 何でも話せる 親友の女の子
Secretly walking home after school, a girl friend I can talk to about anything
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて 女子力 MAX で
Good at sports, smart, and her feminine power is maxed out
どこにでもある よくあること 急に彼女が
It's a common story everywhere, then suddenly she says...
あのね 実は私 好きな人がいるの
You know, actually, there's someone I like
え、ちょっ マジで!?
Eh, wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
ベタな漫画みたいなフラグ
A flag like a cliché manga
まさかね 自分が立てちゃうなんて 残念すぎます!
No way, I can't believe I'm the one setting it up, it's so regrettable!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃって済まないカテゴリー
Just kidding, just kidding, it's a category that's not over yet
恋と友情 ゆらゆら揺れて
Love and friendship, swaying back and forth
なんか青春しちゃってます
I'm doing something like youth
わたし 困っちゃいます
I'm troubled
乾杯です お似合いすぎるわ カテゴリー外
Cheers, you're too good for each other, outside the category
悔しいけど どっか そんなんじゃなくて本心
It's frustrating, but somehow that's not it, it's my true feelings
っていうか すでに 応援モード むしろ清々しい
I mean, I'm already in support mode, actually refreshing
だけど彼女は 不思議な顔 真剣な目で
But she has a strange look on her face, with serious eyes
そうじゃなくて私 あなたが好き ごめん
That's not it, I like you, sorry
え、ちょっ マジで!?
Eh, wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
わたし あなた 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her and me
超絶複雑 百合展開は 想定外ですわ!
Super complex, a yuri development is unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃって済まないカテゴリー
Just kidding, just kidding, it's a category that's not over yet
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
An unsolvable puzzle given to me
神よ 恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I'll resent you
私、悩んじゃいます
I'm troubled.
わぁ、すごいヤバい！
Wow, this is crazy!
好きだよ、好きだけど、ってそういう意味じゃなくって、
I like you, I do, but I don't mean it that way...
だって、女の子同士だし
I mean, we're both girls...
ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
私、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
Help me!
なんか変だ　愛に国境も
Something's weird, love knows no borders,
年も性別も関係ない
no age or gender requirements,
けど、けど、けど…
but, but, but...
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangle love is fickle,
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses.
普通の恋　夢見てたのに
I was dreaming of a normal love,
ノーマル設定の私じゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
but for a normal girl like me, it's too much of a 'garbage game'!
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle love is unstable,
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
A 'just kidding' category isn't enough.
彼女のこと　好きになれたなら
If I could fall in love with her...
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I start daydreaming like that.
私、どうかしてます
I'm losing my mind.
行くよー！
Here we go!
Hae~!
Bau bau!
Thank you, Ruffians!
That was so much fun!
Yeah, though I got a bit dizzy though.
Yeah, the bubble dance and changing so quickly!
It was so fast!
But you know, the bubble dance was a little bit silly, but did we surprise you?
And we got this as well, even more close-up than usual!
Well, the last two songs we sang were "Kiss me! I'm Stayin' Together" with Abvent...
...and "Triangle Dreamer!"
With Miko-senpai, Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
What'd you think, Ruffians?
"Kiss me! I'm Stayin' Together" is a song that I've always wanted to sing together with Abvent.
It's a little bit more sexy... a bit of a sexy song, huh?
And "Triangle Dreamer!" The festival idol song!
So the "Yuritenkai" was too cute...
Ruffians, are you still alive?
Are you alive?
Yeah! Bau bau!
Mio-senpai was so cute in love!
And then crowd-surfing at the end! Woaah!
It was the best! A lot of "firsts" this year, right?
Well, we have a tiny, tiny announcement!
You know, it's FuwaMoco's birthday, right?
Our birthday!
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you!
Okay, let's do it!
Yeah!
Dondon! Papan!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with the FuwaMoco 2026 Birthday Merch!
フワモコの生誕グッズ紹介、始まるよ！
The FuwaMoco birthday merch introduction starts now!
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols with the Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa...
...and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands!
By our mama, Ikomochi-mama!
They're a bit big compared to regular acrylic stands,
so we think they'd be a great addition to your collection!
大きめサイズで可愛いアイドルのフワモコアクリルスタンド！
Big size and cute idol FuwaMoco acrylic stands!
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel and Hoeh!? Devil rubber figurines!
They're now palm-sized figures, perfect for displaying on your desk!
表情豊かなフワモコが、手のひらサイズのラバーマスコットになったよ！
The expressive FuwaMoco have become palm-sized rubber mascots!
This one is big!
We finally have FuwaMoco plushies in our out-and-about casual outfits!
But this time, we also speak when you hug us!
It's the Yappy Puppy FuwaMoco Sounds Plushies!
We'll be the same size as our friends at Youtooz...
So you can display them together!
おしゃべりパピーぬいぐるみのふわもこだよ！
It's the Talking Puppy Plushie FUWAMOCO!
ギュッとするといろいろ喋るよ！
If you squeeze us, we talk!
どんなボイスが出るか、お楽しみに！
I wonder what kind of voices we'll have? Look forward to it!
We have the Fuwawa to GO Finger Puppet! Oh!
They both come with one extra Ruffians mascot costume you can dress us up in and bring us around with you everywhere!
ふわわの指パペット！
Fuwawa's Finger Puppet!
どこでも一緒に連れていけるサイズで、着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もありよ！
They're in a size you can take anywhere, and they come with a Ruffians dress-up costume too!
Finally, we have two different
ASMR voice packs,
"Back from a Fluffy Date" with Fuwawa,
and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo!
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
They made our hearts beat so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them! Oh!
The merch is separated into two sets:
Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the Full Set,
they come with bonuses, including a Cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはふわわセットと、もここセットに分かれています！
The merch is split into a Fuwawa set and a Mococo set!
セットごとにチェキ風カードと、特典ボイスがつきます！
Each set comes with a Cheki-style card and a bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン入りだよ！
The Limited Edition Set comes with a hand-signed autograph!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛情込めてサイン書きますね！
I'll put lots of love into signing them!
Please check out the Hololive Official Online Shop and look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！
Please check out the Hololive Official Shop!
Bau bau! What did you think? Yeah!
Our birthday merch is pretty cute, huh? Yeah! Wow!
The reservations will be going on sale right after the Birthday Live here ends, so don't forget, okay?
生誕のグッズの予約はこの後開始しますので、お忘れずにチェックしてください！
Reservations for the birthday merch start after this, so don't forget to check it out!
You can check the link below, or on the side here! Yeah! Oh! Don't forget, okay?
We put a lot of love into it and Icomochi-mama too!
Thank you, Icomochi-mama! Right after this ends, time to go, go, go! Yeah! Go buy it! Wow!
We performed a more special collab song with our dear Senpai! Yeah!
But there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
まだ会ってない謎のゲストが一人いるんだよね！
There's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Yeah! Oh! Wow! So shall we give the Ruffians a hint? Oh! Huh?
Ruffians, you're curious, right? Yeah!
Who could it be? Who could it be? Yagoo-san? Ah, Yagoo-san! That's a good guess maybe, but...
Well, you'll see! Oh! Maybe you should get ready!
Because you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero, but they can get pretty nasty sometimes! Oh!
Mococo-chan, you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out! Well, we'll see! Oh!
Wow! Let's get them out here then! Who could it be? Who could it be? Okay!
せーの、どうぞ！
One, two... Come on out!
わわわ！ 来たしんよ！ 来たしんよ！
Wa wa wa! I'm here, shin-yo! I'm here, shin-yo!
来たしんよ！ キュンキュン！ チュッチュッチュッ！ あー！
I'm here, shin-yo! Kyun kyun! Chu chu chu! Ah!
自己紹介お願いします！ おー！
Please introduce yourself! Oh!
クロちゃんです！ わわわ！
It's Kuro-chan! Wa wa wa!
Japanese Comedian / Yasuda Dai Circus / Kuro-chan
来たしんよー！
I'm here, shin-yo!
初めまして！ おー！ チワワじゃないよ、ふわわだよ！
Nice to meet you! Oh! I'm not a Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
ふわわじゃないよ、もここだよ！ おー！
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo! Oh!
二人合わせて、ふわもこです！
Together, we are FUWAMOCO!
バウバウ！ よろしくお願いします！ よろしくお願いします！ おー！
Bau Bau! Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Oh!
ふわもこのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to FUWAMOCO's Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
Happy Birthday だしんよ、ふわもこ！ いいしんね！
Happy Birthday, shin-yo, FUWAMOCO! It's great!
ありがとう！ ありがとう！ おー！ ちょっとね、えーと、
Thank you! Thank you! Oh! Um...
視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど、
I think there are many Ruffians watching, so...
クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？ Yeah!
Could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is? Yeah!
自分ですんの？ それ。 Introduction!
I have to do it myself?! Introduction!
わかったしんよ。だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね？
I see, shin-yo. Since people overseas are watching too, right?
海外の人もわかる自己紹介しますからね！ おー！ Okei!
I'll do an introduction that overseas fans will understand too! Oh! Okay!
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! チュッチュッチュッチュッチュ... チューリップ！
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Chu chu chu chu chu... Tulip!
ハッ、おー！ 困らないで！ えー、クロちゃんは、えー、チューリップ？
Huh? Oh! Please don't be confused! Eh, Kuro-chan, 'Tulip'?
いやチューリップ no no no... ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから...
No, Tulip no no no... Wait, they might not understand yet...
えーとね、安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる、
I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus,
えーと、芸人さんで、あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってますし、
and I also produce Mameshiba no Taigun,
作詞とかもしています。クロちゃんです！ おー！
and write lyrics too. I'm Kuro-chan! Oh!
じゃあ今回は英語でお願いします！ In English!
Well, this time, please do it in English! In English!
僕が？！ 自分で？！ Yes？！ えー、そんなこと急に言われたら...
Me?! Myself?! Yes?! Hey, if you say that so suddenly...
はい、パップフラワー！
Yes, Pappu Flower!
ノー、ノー、ノー、言い訳はなし！
No, no, no, no excuses!
いや、聞いてる、人の話。
Hey, listen to what people are saying.
ねえ、頑張って！
Hey, go for it!
ファッション、えーと、なんだっけ、えーと...
Fashion... uh, what was it? Uh...
フェイマスコメディアン！
Famous comedian!
おお！コメディアン！
Oh! Comedian!
あと、アイドルプロデューサー！
And, idol producer!
ややっ、かっこいい！
Wow, so cool!
やってるしんよ！
You're doing it, shin!
おお、できる！
Oh, you can do it!
いいしん！
Nice, shin!
クロちゃん、テレビでよく見てるけど...
Kuro-chan, we see you on TV a lot, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと...
...you look a little bit like FuwaMoco's pet Pero-chan...
...えーと、ちょっと似てるところがたくさんあるね！
...and you have a lot of similarities!
うん！え、ちょっと後ろの...
Yeah! Uh, look at the back...
飾り見てください。見えますか？
decoration. Can you see it?
そうすると、ペロです！
If you do that, it's Pero!
ペロ！
Pero!
ちょっ、待って、球体っていうか、丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait, it's just the round, spherical part that looks like me, right?
ねえ、ペロじゃない！
Hey, isn't it Pero?
本当？
Really?
うん！
Yeah!
えーと、クロちゃんと似てるところは...
The things similar to Kuro-chan are...
嘘つきで...
...he's a liar...
女の子好きで...
...likes girls...
野卑し、うーん！
...and vulgar, yuck!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで！
So don't be fooled by appearances!
クロちゃんはそんなんで大丈夫なの？言われて。
Kuro-chan, are you okay being told all that?
いや、ひどい、悲しくなってきた。
That's terrible, I'm getting sad.
え、え、え、え、え！
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh!
遠歩後援、ふんっ！
Enpo Kouen, humph!
全然人のギャグを聞かないよね、君たちは。
You guys don't listen to my gags at all, do you?
できれば、クロちゃんは...
If possible, Kuro-chan...
ペロの友達になってくれませんか？
...won't you become Pero's friend?
フワモコの友達じゃなくてペロの友達なの？
Not FuwaMoco's friend, but Pero's friend?
あ、フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから！
Ah, because FuwaMoco doesn't want to be friends with Kuro-chan!
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that strange?
いや、いや、気持ち悪いから！
No, no, because it's gross!
いや、気持ち悪くない、マニアには受ける！
It's not gross, it'll be popular with the manias!
いや、違う！
No way!
フワモコ気持ち悪い、やっぱり！
FuwaMoco thinks it's gross after all!
でも、でも、モコちゃん...
But, but, Moko-chan...
ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼ですよ。
...you're going a bit too far, it's rude.
いや、もし、もし、ペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら...
Well, if, if you want me to get along with Pero...
フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだほうがいいんじゃない？
...FuwaMoco-chan should ask Kuro-chan cutely, shouldn't you?
はぁ〜〜？！
Haa~~?!
ノー！
No!
え、ノー！
Eh, no!
ノー！
No!
しっかりとした否定。
Such a firm denial.
え、ま、けど、ペロ可愛いから、仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ。
Well, Pero is cute, so I think it's okay to get along.
あ、嬉しい、嬉しい、嬉しい！
Oh, happy, happy, happy!
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな！
He's not cute, but I'd be happy if you got along!
感情が、感情がいろいろありすぎなのよ、本当に。
You have, you have way too many conflicting emotions, really.
まあまあ。
Now, now.
クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？
Kuro-chan is a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
ね！
Right!
そう、もともとアイドルになろうと思ったのに、騙されて芸人にさせられたから。
Yeah, originally I intended to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian.
アイドルは本当に夢、ドリーム。
Being an idol is really a dream, a dream.
あ、なんか悲しいな、かわいそう。
Oh, that's a bit sad, poor thing.
失礼です、でもドリームって大事ですから！
That's rude, but dreams are important!
大事！
Important!
うん。さ、で、ま、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから...
Yeah. So, since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol...
...もうせっかく一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
...won't you sing together with us since we're here?
あ！いいしんや、いいしんや！
Ah! Good, shin, good, shin!
オッケーだしんよ、歌って踊れるしんね！
It's okay, shin, I can sing and dance too, shin!
うん、この曲、次の曲ね！
Yeah, this song, the next song!
あの、ハードル上げないで！
Um, don't raise the hurdle!
え、大丈夫ですよ、ね！
Eh, it's fine, right!
アイドルのプロデューサーもやってるし！
You're an idol producer too!
そうそう、実力見せてよ！
Right, right, show us your skills!
ねえ、見せて！
Hey, show us!
オッケーだしんよ、行くしんよ、行くしんよ！
It's okay, shin, I'm going, shin, I'm going, shin!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a very cute song together!
え、何なんだろ、楽しみに！
Eh, what is it? I'm looking forward to it!
オッケー！
Okay!
うん。
Yeah.
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！
Then, let's do the title call together!
ね！
Right!
うん。
Yeah.
せーの！
Ready, set...
ちゅ、多様性！
Chu, Tayousei!
ちゅ、多様性あんの？！
You're doing 'Chu, Tayousei'?!
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
Lyrics: あの, 真部脩一 - Music: 真部脩一
Lyrics: ano, Shuichi Mabe - Music: Shuichi Mabe
我愛你　酔いが醒めない
I love you, I can't sober up
Oh I need you　恋が醒めない
Oh I need you, I can't wake up from love
お生様の成れ果て召して
Feast upon the ruins of a raw existence
無問題　破滅してみて
No problem, try being ruined
Hold me tight　トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対　お手お座りで
Strong opposition, with 'paw' and 'sit'
ヘイ♥報酬
Hey, reward
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat prickles
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Try erasing loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も全廃して
Abolish all love and romance
僕を独占して
Monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまで
Until you become addicted like this
ちゅ（しよう）
Let's kiss
Get get get on!
Get get get on! Get on chu!
熱くとろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
Feelings overflowing enough to melt hotly
たまらないでしょ
It's irresistible, right?
Get get get on!
Get get get on! Get on chu!
我愛你　無問題
I love you, no problem
Get Get Get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン　勝負はいつも
Pon, Chi, Kan, the match is always...
トンチンカン　僕に言わせて
...absurd, let me say it
ちんぷんかんぷんだ　最後はロンでしょ？
It's all Greek to me, the end is 'Ron', right?
もう何回？　殺られればいい
How many more times? It's fine to be killed
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, I can't forget it
終わんないでトキメキ偏愛♡予習
Don't let it end, this heart-fluttering偏愛 prep♡
喉の奥がチクンチクン
Deep in my throat, it pricks and pricks
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping and thumping
心臓ごと引きずり出してみせてよ
Try and drag out my entire heart
気持ちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, even if it's a hassle
やっぱ照れくさいけど
I guess it's embarrassing, after all
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよう
Let's have a kiss we'll never forget until we die
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me
ときめく胸に繋がるロープを
Pull the rope connected...
引きなよ
...to your throbbing chest
いくよ
Here we go!
Bet bet bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの美しさが
Such a level of beauty that could truly drive one mad
美しいでしょ
Is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on chu!
せーの
One, two...
ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Pon-Chi-Kan, it won't end
Get Get Get on chu!
ほらね
See?
我愛你 無問題
I love you, no problem
Get Get Get on chu!
わー！うまくいったしんよー！
Wow! It went well-shin!
ありがとうー！よかったー！がんばったね、クロちゃん！
Thank you! That was great! You did your best, Kuro-chan!
楽しかった、ありがとう！
That was fun, thank you!
えー、ちょっとね、さよならする前に...
Um, well, before we say goodbye...
えっと、一個お願いしてもいいですか？
...could we ask you for one favor?
一個だけだしんよ？
Just one thing-shin?
一個だけじゃん！
Just one thing, okay!
えっと、フワモコは魔界の番犬で、バウバウをよく言ってるんですけど
Well, Fuwamoco are guard dogs of the Underworld, and we often say "Bau Bau."
クロちゃん、カメラに向かってフワモコのように可愛いバウバウをしてもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, could you do a cute "Bau Bau" for the camera, just like Fuwamoco?
えー、できるかなー？行くしんよ！
Eh, can I do it? Here I go-shin!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
あー！バウバウ！それがベスト！
Ah! Bau Bau! That was the best!
もう一回！もっとやって！
One more time! Do it more!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
可愛いかな？
Was that cute?
実はもう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど
Actually, there's one more thing we want to do.
なに？
What is it?
さきほどやりましたけど、フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって
We did it earlier, but Fuwamoco has a self-introduction we always do.
できれば三人で一緒にやりたいです！
If possible, we want to do it with all three of us!
あれ可愛かったからやりたいしんよ！
That was cute, so I want to do it-shin!
じゃあ、いきますよ！
Okay, here we go!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよ！
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
ワワワワワ！フワワじゃないよ、クロちゃんだよ！
Wawawawawa! I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Kuro-chan!
クロちゃんじゃないよ、モココだよ！
I'm not Kuro-chan, I'm Mococo!
三人に合わせて、アイヤイヤイヤイ！バウバウ！
All three of us together, Aiyaiyaiyai! Bau Bau!
なんなの、怒らないで、どうしたの？
What's wrong? Don't get mad. What happened?
でででで、クロちゃん！
Dededede, Kuro-chan!
出てこないから、なんなのそれ？
I'm not coming out. What's that about?
おい、もう嘘つくのやめてよね！
Hey, stop lying already!
じゃないと、モココ、パンチしちゃうぞ！
Otherwise, Mococo will punch you!
えだ... ちょちょちょちょ...
Wait... whoa whoa whoa...
やー！
Yaah!
救急車一台...
Call an ambulance...
いらないよ、もう嘘ばっかり、なんなのそれ？
We don't need one! You're just full of lies, what was that?
バウバウ... なんでバウバウ怒るの、ちょっと
Bau Bau... why are you getting mad at "Bau Bau"?
落ち着いて、落ち着いて
Calm down, calm down.
大丈夫、モコちゃん、大丈夫
It's okay, Mococo-chan, it's okay.
クロちゃんはこれからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
なるしんよ！バウバウ！
I will-shin! Bau Bau!
じゃあ、モコちゃん
Well then, Mococo-chan...
最後にクロちゃんとハイタッチしてお別れしようね
...let's end with a high touch with Kuro-chan before saying goodbye.
オッケー、仲直り、仲直り、いい？
Okay. Reconciliation, reconciliation, okay?
仲直りね、オッケーしんよ。はい、ハイタッチ！
Reconciliation, right. Okay-shin. Here, high touch!
ほらほらほらほら！やってみて、やってみて！仲直り！
Come on, come on! Give it a try! Reconciliation!
ベー！
Bleh!
ひどくない、もうちょっと！なんなの？バイバイ！
Isn't that cruel? Seriously! What gives? Bye-bye!
フワモコちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Fuwamoco-chan, happy birthday, for real!
おめでとう！ありがとうー！バウバウ！
Congratulations! Thank you! Bau Bau!
クロちゃんからの、バッキューン！おめでとう、ハート！
A "Bakyuun" from Kuro-chan! Congrats, heart!
ステイゴールド！
Stay gold!
Fireworks!
Bau Bau! Look at the fireworks!
たーまやー！かーぎやー！
Tamaya! Kagiya!
First anniversary...
...we released our very...
...first original song,
Born to be BAU-DOL!
Yeah!
And then for our second anniversary...
...we were able to release Lifetime Showtime!
Oh!
Our original song that's grown with us along this journey.
Yeah.
A very special song.
And you know,
for FUWAMOCO, singing and dancing is something that means so much to us.
Yeah, music!
And Ruffians,
you might've heard that you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Yeah! Yeah!
What do you think, yeah?
Oh... wow!
Our announcement is...
Drumroll...
Drumroll!
(Popepopepopepope!)
Done!
A new original song!
Oh!
Its title is "DEMON'S RESIDENCE"!
And...
This song is extra special.
Yeah!
It's written by none other than the legendary rock idol song composer, Matsukuma Kenta-san...
...who works with many famous idol groups that we love!
Oh!
Also written music
for the idol group that Kuro-chan produced,
MAMESHIBA NO TAIGUN-san!
Yeah!
But Ruffians,
you might be a little bit surprised, okay?
Oh!
So get ready!
Ruffians,
with this song,
we'd like to express our Ruff-est feelings...
...as demon dogs!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
Lyrics: FUWAMOCO Music: 松隈ケンタ
Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
Lyrics: FUWAMOCO Music: Kenta Matsukuma
Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"My partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
We pass by the neon lights
バブルガムがはじけたら
When the bubblegum pops
let's go
最低な夜を潜って
Passing through the worst of nights
僕らは群れをなす
We form a pack
「あの頃よりもマシだね」
"It's better than back then"
my way
「不完全なんです」
"We are incomplete"
首輪をつけた
We put on our collars
良い子なんじゃもう
We don't want to be good girls anymore
イヤ Ah!!
No way, ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 噛みついていけ
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, bite through it
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
気分はどうだい
How does it feel?
泣いているのかい
Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
We want to keep screaming,
stray dogs
彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を
The birds flying to the distance
見上げるだけかい
Are you just looking up?
それでいいのかい？
Is that enough for you?
燃えるならほら
If we're going to burn, look,
青く
let's burn blue
「説教なんかいらない」
"We don't need any lectures"
スプレー缶振って
Shake the spray can
イタズラ書きで
Painting the runway
彩る runway
with graffiti
愛情なんか coin toss
Love is like a coin toss
誰に bet するのか
Who are you betting on?
不確定要素ばかりね
It's full of uncertain elements,
lonely
二人でひとつと
We decided the two of us
決めた
were one
あの日を忘れない
We won't forget that day
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
満天の空
A sky full of stars
あの星がひどく不快で
Those stars are so unpleasant
勝利はどうだい
How is victory?
味がするのかい？
Can you taste it?
鎖を噛んで
Biting the chains
唸っていたいんだ
We want to keep growling,
stray dogs
僕ら空さえも撃ち落として
We'll even shoot down the sky
見下ろす奈落
Looking down at the abyss
ビルは輝く
The buildings are glowing
LOL Now I am free!!
孤独を分け合い
Sharing and eating
食べた
our loneliness
あの日を忘れない
We won't forget that day
鳴呼
Ah
夜を睨んだ
Staring into the night,
stray dogs
そうだ
That's right
怪物はこの世のほうさ
The monsters are the world itself
抜け出せるのかい
Can you escape?
足は動くかい
Can your legs move?
走るなら今
If you're going to run, now's the time
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
stray dogs
僕ら
We
この街を駆け抜けていけ
Race through this city
地獄の果てに何が見えるかい
What can you see at the end of hell?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
We want to keep screaming,
stray dogs
僕ら
We
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
君ならどうだい
How about you?
共に駆けるかい
Will you run with us?
夜明けが合図だ
Dawn is the signal
行こう
Let's go
Bau Bau!
Thank you for always being here for us Ruffians!
Please listen to...
side by side!
Finally we made it through
but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true
we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate
all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on passed the heartbreak
and the sorrow
If you stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there were tough times
when nobody wanted us
We kept going, and we kept dreaming
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore
We'll be here together,
with our smiles to protect
C'mon, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya nya nya nya nya...
Bau Bau!
Bau Bau! Thank you for the encore Ruffians!
That was side by side! Bau Bau!
We're really happy we could perform side by side
for the first time live today!
え、初披露できてとっても
Uhh, I'm so happy we could perform it for the first time
side by side is a song made by Alobahn-san,
but also between FUWAMOCO!
We know it's a song that you love a lot, but we also too,
because it's very special to us since it's the ending
theme for a visual novel that we care about...
Nekopara! Nekopara! Bau Bau!
And with this song, our dream of singing the opening
or ending theme for a bishoujo game came true!
そう、この曲で FUWAMOCO の夢、
Yes, with this song, FUWAMOCO's dream,
美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
of singing a theme song for a bishoujo game has come true!
Thank you! Thank you! ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us
for our special day again this year!
It's been a dream of ours!
And you know, it's all because of you
that we're able to be here
and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you!
We say, but...
Ah...
This next song is our last song.
But like what we said at the special one, you know FuwaMoco...
...is Demon Guard Dogs! We're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that.
Protect your smile.
Yeah, through our arts, idol,
And just as our fluffy and fuzzy souls too.
Yeah.
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of Demon Dog years,
while remembering that, you know, every day isn't given.
Yeah.
We don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down, we hope that you remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We're cheering you on, Ruffians!
So please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today.
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow and the day after too
あなたが笑ってますように
May you be smiling
ずっと...
Forever...
Lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
Wishful☆Garnet / Lyrics, Music: 黒崎ジョン
Wishful☆Garnet / Lyrics, Music: John Kurosaki
Please think of this song whenever things are rough, and know that we'll be here.
This last song is for you! Wishful☆Garnet!
過去を振り返ると　思い出す
Looking back at the past, I remember
ガーネットの空
The garnet sky
溢れていく　光
The light that overflows
この目に映し出されたあの日は
On that day reflected in these eyes
美しく　揺れる
It sways beautifully
What do you think?
赤く滲んだ空に
In the red-tinted sky
願いました　どうかこの願い
I made a wish, please let this wish
届けてください
Reach you
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow and the day after too
あなたが笑ってますように
May you be smiling
離ればなれになっても　前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, may you look forward
あなたを縛る鎖を　わたしが壊してあげる
The chains that bind you, I will break them for you
もう負けないで進むこと
Keep moving forward without giving in
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I'm always by your side
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when you're depressed or lose confidence
目の前にいてくれる
You're right there in front of me
あなたの笑顔に何度も救われた
I was saved many times by your smile
だから So I love you
That's why, So I love you
挫けそうになったら
When you feel like you're about to give up
手を伸ばして　まだ知らない明日
Reach out your hand, to the tomorrow you don't know yet
一緒に見つけよう
Let's find it together
明日も　明後日も　あなたを照らしていたい
Tomorrow and the day after too, I want to keep lighting you up
泣きそうになった時は　こっち向いてほしい
When you're about to cry, I want you to look this way
世界でひとりぼっち　そんな風に思わないで
Don't feel like you're all alone in the world
愛してくれる人は　きっと
There are surely people who love you
いつもあなたを想ってる
Always thinking of you
Uuu... Yeah...
Wishful Garnet
La la la...
願いました　どうかこの願い
I made a wish, please let this wish
届けてください
Reach you
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow and the day after too
あなたが笑ってますように
May you be smiling
離ればなれになっても　前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, may you look forward
あなたを縛る鎖を　わたしが壊してあげる
The chains that bind you, I will break them for you
もう負けないで進むこと
Keep moving forward without giving in
輝く空へ
To the shining sky
明日も　明後日も　あなたが笑ってますように
Tomorrow and the day after, I hope you'll be smiling
離ればなれになっても前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, I hope you'll be able to look forward
あなたを縛る鎖をわたしが壊してあげる　woh woh
I will break the chains that bind you, woh woh
もう負けないで進むこと
Don't lose and keep moving forward
いつでもそばに　あなたのそばに
Always by your side, right next to you
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I'll always be there
La la la...
Oh yeah...
Bau Bau!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
Bau Bau!
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
We're waiting for you at our members-only encore live!